<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Embedded Systems on Jacob R. Stevens</title>
    <link>https://jakestevens.github.io/tags/embedded-systems/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content in Embedded Systems on Jacob R. Stevens</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2017 Jacob R. Stevens</copyright>
    <atom:link href="/tags/embedded-systems/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>TrackRx</title>
      <link>https://jakestevens.github.io/project/track-rx/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jakestevens.github.io/project/track-rx/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TrackRx is a wireless, internet-connected pill bottle designed to solve the adherence and abuse problem, designed by a four-member team in one semester for Purdue University’s ECE 477 Digital Systems Senior Design Project Course. It makes it easier for patients to take their medication correctly and harder for them to abuse prescription medications by dispensing a single dose of medication at a time and providing medication adherence data in real-time to the patient’s pharmacist, doctor, and other caretakers. Along with the pill bottle itself, the TrackRx system consists of an Android app for the patient, a desktop application for the pharmacist/doctor, and a backend database and cloud service to communicate with the bottle and applications and securely store patient prescription and adherence information. Taken together, TrackRx is an innovative system which improves upon the standard pill bottle and prescription process with the goal of coming substantially closer to solving the problem of prescription drug adherence and abuse. TrackRx was awarded 2nd place in Purdue ECE&amp;rsquo;s Spark Challenge in Spring of 2016, and was named &amp;ldquo;Best Use of Wireless Technology&amp;rdquo; in Texas Instrument&amp;rsquo;s Innovation Challenge in 2016.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A link to the TI repository can be found &lt;a href=&#34;https://e2e.ti.com/group/universityprogram/students/m/students_repository/666558&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; and a link to the Github repository for this project can be found &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/TrackRxProject&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
